{
  "data":[
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "What is the CSS property for changing the size of an element?",
      "answer": "width",
      "a": "size",
      "b": "weight",
      "c": "width",
      "d": "wide"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "What is the CSS property for containing the exceedings of elements in a container?",
      "answer": "flex-wrap",
      "a": "flex",
      "b": "flex-direction",
      "c": "contain",
      "d": "flex-wrap"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "What is the closing tag for the HTML structure?",
      "answer": "</html>",
      "a": "<html/>",
      "b": "<html>",
      "c": "</html>",
      "d": "</Html>"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "What is the CSS property for curving the sharp edges of an element?",
      "answer": "border-radius",
      "a": "border-line",
      "b": "curver",
      "c": "border-arc",
      "d": "border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "What is the difference between inline CSS, embedded CSS, and external CSS?",
      "answer": "Inline CSS is placed inside the HTML document, embedded CSS is placed outside the `<head>` tag, and external CSS is placed in a separate file.",
      "a": "Inline CSS is placed outside the HTML document, embedded CSS is placed inside the `<head>` tag,and external CSS is placed in a separate file.",
      "b": "Inline CSS is placed inside the HTML document, embedded CSS is placed inside the `<head>` tag,and external CSS is placed in a separate file.",
      "c": "Inline CSS is placed inside the HTML document, embedded CSS is placed outside the `<head>` tag, and external CSS is placed in a separate file.",
      "d": "Inline CSS is placed inside the HTML document, embedded CSS is placed inside the `<head>` tag,and external CSS is placed in the same file."
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "Which of the following tag is used to embed css in html page?",
      "answer": "<style></style>",
      "a": "<css>",
      "b": "<!DOCTYPE html>",
      "c": "<script></script>",
      "d": "<style></style>"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": " Which of the following CSS selectors are used to specify a group of elements?",
      "answer": "class",
      "a": "tag",
      "b": "id",
      "c": "class",
      "d": "id and class"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": " Which of the following has introduced text, list, box, margin, border, color, and background properties?",
      "answer": "CSS",
      "a": "HTML",
      "b": "PHP",
      "c": "CSS",
      "d": "JAVASCRIPT"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": " Which of these is not a programming languages?",
      "answer": "CSS",
      "a": "JAVA",
      "b": "PHP",
      "c": "CSS",
      "d": "JAVASCRIPT"
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": " Which of the following is the correct syntax to link an external style sheet in the HTML file?",
      "answer": " <link rel=”stylesheet” href=”style.css” />",
      "a": " <link rel=”stylesheet” href=”style.css” />",
      "b": "<link rel=”stylesheet” src=”style.css” />",
      "c": "<style rel=”stylesheet” src=”style.css” />",
      "d": " <style rel=”stylesheet” link=”style.css” />"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": " which of these is a type of styling",
      "answer": " all of the above",
      "a": "inline styling",
      "b": "embedded styling",
      "c": "external styling",
      "d": " all of the above"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": " which of css properties is used to change the text color ",
      "answer": " color",
      "a": "font-size",
      "b": "color",
      "c": "background-color",
      "d": " all of the above"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": " which of css properties is used to change the text colour ",
      "answer": " color",
      "a": "font-size",
      "b": "color",
      "c": "background-color",
      "d": " all of the above"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "In building a website, we must first?",
      "answer": "boxify",
      "a": "call display flex",
      "b": "boxify",
      "c": "do the styling",
      "d": "Do justify content"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "Question": "_____ is the major difference between Notepad and Visual Studio Code",
      "answer": "VSCode allows you use intelliscence while Notepad does not",
      "a": "Visual Studio Code is for cuilding websites while notepad is used for webApp",
      "b": "Notepad is used for CSS while VSCode is used for HTML ",
      "c": "Notepad allows you use intelliscence while VSCode does not",
      "d": "VSCode allows you use intelliscence while Notepad does not"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "Question": "Which of the following statement(s) is/are correct?",
      "answer": "CSS is only used for styling",
      "a": "HTML is only used for building Websites",
      "b": "CSS is only used for styling",
      "c": "Microsoft Excel is a text editor ",
      "d": "HTML is used for styling"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "Question": "We create _______ in a folder",
      "answer": "files",
      "a": "cells",
      "b": "components",
      "c": "files",
      "d": "tables"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "Question": "Which is the first component of a website?",
      "answer": "Header",
      "a": "Body",
      "b": "Header",
      "c": "Footer",
      "d": "Sider"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "Question": "HTML tags are usually enclosed in?",
      "answer": "Angular brackets",
      "a": "Curly braces",
      "b": "Square brackets",
      "c": "parenthesis",
      "d": "Angular brackets"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "Question": "all HTML tags are closed",
      "answer": "False",
      "a": "True",
      "b": "False",
      "c": "Maybe",
      "d": "Certainly"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "Question": "In order to style a div in html, we give it a _________",
      "answer": "class",
      "a": "class",
      "b": "color",
      "c": "width",
      "d": "height"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "Question": "Carpenter is to Hammer and Nail as Developer is to?",
      "answer": "Laptop and Smart Phone",
      "a": "Rows and columns",
      "b": "Text and Images",
      "c": "Laptop and Smart Phone",
      "d": "Signs and Symbols"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "Question": "The title tag is enclosed in what tag?",
      "answer": "Head tag",
      "a": "Head tag",
      "b": "Body tag",
      "c": "div tag",
      "d": "None of the above"
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "Question": "Majority of our codes are found in the?",
      "answer": "Body tag",
      "a": "Head tag",
      "b": "Body tag",
      "c": "div tag",
      "d": "None of the above"
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "Question": "All these are not html tags except?",
      "answer": "strong tag",
      "a": "<i/> tag",
      "b": "<p/> tag",
      "c": "strong tag",
      "d": "<style></style>"
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "Question": " The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is -",
      "answer": "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
      "a": "Head, Title, HTML, body",
      "b": "HTML, Body, Title, Head",
      "c": "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
      "d": "HTML, Head, Title, Body"
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "Question": " which of the following is not part of the heading tag in html?",
      "answer": "<br></br>",
      "a": "<h1></h1>",
      "b": "<h3></h3>",
      "c": "<br></br>",
      "d": "<h4></h4>"
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "Question": "Which of the following tag is used for inserting the largest heading in HTML?",
      "answer": "<h1></h1>",
      "a": "<h1></h1>",
      "b": "<h3></h3>",
      "c": "<h5></h5>",
      "d": "<h4></h4>"
    }
  ]
}